http://www.myabarth.com/privacy

Contact
Promote Us!
Registered users
Username:
Password:
Remember Me?
Random image
Advertisement - Click and support myAbarth.com Community!
Privacy
Introduction
myAbarth.com believes that the responsible use of personal information is critical to the continued success of the Internet. As such, we are committed to the highest standards in protecting and safeguarding your right to privacy while using and interacting with our Web site.
While you can access most areas of our Web site without submitting any personal data, there are certain areas of our site that request specific personal information including name (login), password and e-mail address. Our intent is to allow you as much control as possible over your personal information. Below we explain how myAbarth.com collects, stores, and uses your information.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Data Collection Overview
Server Logs: For each visitor to the myAbrth Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name, browser type, operating system, entry page, exit page, and average time on the Web site. This information is used for internal purposes only in helping us improve our Web site and better your overall experience.
Online Forms: We use online forms in several areas of our Web site. Online forms provide site visitors with an opportunity to request company and product information, request product downloads. All information provided by the visitor is voluntary, with information generally including name, address, company, and e-mail. We will sometimes use this information to contact visitors for marketing, sales, service and support purposes.
Site Feedback Survey: The myAbarth Web site feedback survey is a voluntary questionnaire that solicits visitor feedback on your experience using the myAbarth Web site. Visitors remain anonymous unless they choose to provide their name and e-mail address. Information is used to better the myAbarth Web site and provide a more engaging and useful experience for site visitors.
Contest & Promotions: When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, mailing address, and e-mail address so that we can administer the contest and notify winners.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Cookies
When used properly, cookies can improve the utility of a site by being able to securely store and apply personal data that visitors have voluntarily shared with the site.
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personal identification information, but they do enable us to store site preferences, form information between visits, and items in your shopping cart. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent such acceptance. Doing so, however, may result in disabling the functionality we have in place to better serve your needs.
We use cookies to personalize the experience of our visitors, provide support to customers, record visitor preferences, provide personalized and specialized content, record session information, track visitor clickstream behavior throughout the Web site, track items in your shopping cart and customize site content based on your browser type, operating system, and preferences.
For more detailed information about cookies, what they are, and why they are used, please visit the following Web site (not affiliated with myAbarth.com): http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/index.shtml.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Web Bugs
myAbarth.com does not use Web bugs or any other type of "hidden detection and tracking" technology or coding in its web pages.
Web bugs, or clear GIFs, are tiny images embedded in a Web page or HTML-enhanced e-mail that transmit information to a remote computer when the page is viewed. Businesses operating on the Internet often use them to track visitor behavior or to measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns.
For more detailed information about web bugs, what they are, and why and how they are used, please visit the PrivacyFoundation Web site (not affiliated with myAbarth): http://www.privacyfoundation.org/education/webbug.html.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
E-mail Addresses
We do not collect e-mail addresses without the site visitor voluntarily providing us with this information (typically via our online information request form, whitepaper request form, myAbarth newsletter subscription form, and other Web site forms and surveys).
We will periodically use your e-mail information for service, sales, support, and marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive e-mail from us in the future, please contact us.
>From time to time, we share your e-mail address with other organizations and companies whose products or services we think you may find interesting. If you would like to be included in our "do not share" list, please contact us.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Postal Addresses (Snail Mail)
We do not collect postal addresses without the site visitor voluntarily providing us with this information (typically via our online information request form, whitepaper request form, myAbarth e-Flash! newsletter subscription form, and other Web site forms and surveys).
We will periodically use your postal address information for service, sales, support, and marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive postal mailings from us in the future, please contact us.
>From time to time, we share your postal address with other organizations and companies whose products or services we think you may find interesting. If you would like to be included in our "do not share" list, please contact us.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Telephone Numbers
We do not collect telephone numbers without the site visitor voluntarily providing us with this information (typically via our online information request form, whitepaper request form, myAbarth e-Flash! newsletter subscription form, and other Web site forms and surveys).
We will periodically use your telephone information to contact you regarding service, sales, support, and marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive calls from us in the future, please contact us.
>From time to time, we share your telephone number with other organizations and companies whose products or services we think you may find interesting. If you would like to be included in our "do not share" list, please contact us.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Information Disclosure We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can instruct us not by contacting us.
We may release account information when myAbarth believes, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with the law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of myAbarth, our visitors, or others.
Upon request, myAbarth will provide site visitors with access to their personal information that we have on record. This may include unique identifier information (e.g., visitor number or password information), transaction information (e.g., dates on which visitors made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), and contact information (e.g., name, address, e-mail, and phone number information) as well as communications (e.g., e-mails and completed forms) that the visitor directed to our site.
Visitors can request their personal information at any time by contacting us. We will make every effort to ensure your right to privacy by reviewing, qualifying and validating Visitor Information Requests before disseminating such information.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Security: Online and Offline We have licensed the industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that permits encryption of potentially sensitive information such as your name, address and credit card number. This will make your information unusable in the event of unauthorized third-party interception.
Additionally, we have appropriate security measures in place at our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Other Web Sites & Your Privacy Concerns
Our Web site contains links to other company and organizational Web sites that are not owned or operated by myAbarth. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. For more information on your privacy rights with regards to these sites, please refer to the privacy policies of each respective site that you visit.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Policy Changes By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by myAbart. From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. All privacy policy changes and updates will be promptly posted on our Web site.
Feedback
Our continuing goal is to protect and safeguard your right to privacy. As such, we appreciate all feedback that helps us improve our privacy policy. Please share with us your thoughts, comments, and suggestions.
Regards
Pawel Sokolowski
myAbarth.com Community Founder
© Copyright myAbarth.com - Abarth Community
| Photo Engine: 4 images | Site Engine/Template: Eline.pl - Pawel Sokolowski | Base Template: OsDesigner
